<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PopularMovies</string>

    <!-- Movie Detail-->
    <string name="movie_title">Title</string>
    <string name="movie_ratings">Ratings</string>
    <string name="movie_release_date">Release Date</string>
    <string name="movie_description">Description</string>

    <!-- Build URL keys and values-->
    <!-- Keys-->
    <string name="api_key">api_key</string>
    <string name="settings_sort_key" translatable="false">sort_by</string> <!-- Used in preference screen and uri query build-->
    <!-- Values-->
    <string name="api_key_value">3bc5452a3c521649c0b418627ea7ddab</string>
    <string name="settings_sort_default_value" translatable="false">@string/settings_sort_popularity_value</string> <!-- Used in preference screen and uri query build-->
    <!-- End build URL-->

    <!-- Label values for sort by popularity option [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="settings_sort_popularity_value" translatable="false">popularity.desc</string>
    <string name="settings_sort_popularity_asc_value" translatable="false">popularity.asc</string>

    <!-- Put exclusive String Values for preference fragment screen -->
    <!-- Radiobutton select option-->
    <string-array name="settings_sort_by_values">
        <item>@string/settings_sort_popularity_value</item>
        <item>@string/settings_sort_popularity_asc_value</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Preference fragment titles-->
    <string name="settings_sort_label">Sort by</string>

    <!-- Labels for radioButton-->
    <string-array name="settings_sort_by_labels">
        <item>Descending</item>
        <item>Ascending</item>
    </string-array>
    <!-- End preference Screen strings-->

    <!-- Menu item title Strings -->
    <string name="settings_menu_item">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_movieReview">Movie Reviews</string>
    <!-- End Menu item-->

    <string name="settings_title">Movies Settings</string>
    <string name="movie_details_title">Movie Details</string>

    <string name="test_review">“Ad Astra” is one of the most cerebral sci-fi films I’ve ever seen.
        The original story from writer / director James Gray gives an intimate look at the emotional toll that comes from
        being just one man lost among the stars in the vastness of space. It’s like a more existential version of Terrence Malik’s
        “Tree of Life,” but set in the outer reaches of our galaxy.\r\n\r\nRoy McBride (Brad Pitt), an astronaut with nerves of steel, travels
        to Neptune to find his missing hero astronaut father (Tommy Lee Jones). As part of a top secret mission, Roy begins to unravel a mystery and uncover
        truths that may threaten the survival of Earth. This may sound like a blockbuster action thriller, but it’s not. Instead, the film is an emotionally
        complex introspective about a man burdened with the sins of his father.\r\n\r\nPitt gives a stunning, understated performance as a man struggling with
        the psychological toll of isolation and regret. It’s one of his best to date, and it’s nearly impossible not to have a deep emotional connection as you
        share his character’s established sadness. The father and son dynamic shapes Roy’s life, and he’s never quite gotten over the abandonment issues he’s
        felt since he was a child. The scenes where Roy and Cliff finally reunite are brief but come from a heartfelt place of forgiveness that grows with the
        passage of time. It’s the perfect analysis of our own humanity, as we all continue searching with a blind hope to find our footing in the cosmos.\r\n\r\nThe
        film relies heavily on voiceover narration from Roy, something I normally hate because it feels like lazy storytelling. That isn’t the case here. It works well
        and is a very effective method that complements the director’s vision. In fact, everything about this film is a success, from Max Richter‘s haunting original score
        to the special effects and striking cinematography (by Hoyte Van Hoytema), tight direction, and detailed sound design. Gray achieves what he’s going for when every
        element of the film works together as a whole, and it all is executed in a stunning fashion.\r\n\r\n“Ad Astra” is highly intelligent and melancholy science fiction
        that will leave a lasting impression on those who can appreciate its sadness and beauty.
    </string>
    <string name="text_author">Louisa Moore - Screen Zealots</string>
    <string name="review_readMore">Read More</string>
</resources>
